

josh@designerdean.com 801-859-2674 9124 Daybreak Circle Sandy, UT 84093 www.designerdean.com twitter.com/joshdean github.com/designerdean codepen.io/designerdean

Profile: Hardworking and highly organized User Experience Designer/Engineer with 7 years of experience. Currently directing the Digital Department at Saxton Horne Communications, a creative agency.

EXPERIENCE

Saxton Horne Communications in Sandy, Utah from February 2012 to Present Digital Lead & User Experience Engineer

- Leading the creation of client websites through <u>information architecture</u>, <u>wireframes</u>, prototypes, visual design, and development
- Directing and managing members of Digital Department including user experience designers and backend engineers
- Writing semantic and accessible HTML and responsive, organized, and DRY CSS/Sass
- · Conducting usability tests and producing formal usability studies at strategic points during website creation process

a la mode, **inc.** in Salt Lake City, Utah from September 2010 to February 2012 **Product Designer**

- Designed FormMobi.com web application UI and developed accompanying HTML/CSS
- · Redefined and redesigned website products for real estate professionals

IBFX in Salt Lake City, Utah from November 2007 to September 2010 **Web Designer**

- Led redesign of domestic and international customer websites through information architecture, wireframes, prototypes, design mockups, and front-end development
- · Designed and developed HTML/CSS of customer and corporate websites
- Designed and developed HTML emails and landing pages

Eastland Properties, Inc. in Holladay, Utah from August 2004 to November 2007 **REALTOR® / Web Designer**

- Marketed properties for sale to potential buyers, established and met contract deadlines and obligations
- Designed and developed brokerage website focused on marketing to potential clients

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF DENVER

Master of Communication with a specialty in Public Relations and Marketing, To be awarded November 2014

UNIVERSITY OF UTAH

Bachelor of Arts in English, Awarded 2006